TuanAnh Tran (Anh)

Game Developer - Web developer - Business/Data analyst

Prisbane, QLD, Australia

(+61) 480 355 031

Sir-Apple

https://tranquangtuananh28.wixsite.com/tuananhtran

SadApple

TuanAnh Tran

Passionate and motivated in web and game development. Detail-oriented in problem solving and planning. Ready to make an immediate contribution to your organization. Hardworking and patient, able to manage others while working autonomously to complete tasks. Experience working effectively on various teams to exceed expectations and meet goals. Curiosity and willingness to learn and quickly adapt to new skills and environments.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

APPLICATION DEVELOPER / Internship

Premier Ducts, Brisbane, QLD | 09/2021 - 03/2022

(About Premier Ducts: a small duct-manufacturing workshop and company)

Tasks: Created a small app for internal usage

- Worked in the company's office with a small group of developers (three, including one senior developer). My responsibilities included designing and implementing the front-end and user experience of an internal application used by duct workers in the workshop. I also programmed several app features, including generating new stations using C#. Initially, the app was meant to be developed with Unity Engine and C#, but it was later switched to Xamarin.
- My primary responsibility was ensuring that the app met the requirements necessary for managing the duct workers, allowing them to track their work in each station more easily. The app is mainly used by workers on their company-provided phones.
- The skills, tools, and programming languages I utilized during this project included MySQL, front-end development, C#, Unity Engine, and Xamarin.

NETWORK SECURITY ANALYTICS / Internship

VCyber, HoChiMinh City, Vietnam | 07/2021 - 12/2021

(Company website: https://vcyber.io)

Tasks: Researched on cybersecurity technologies

- Worked with an average team of 8-9 members through online workshop meetings that occurred 3-4 days a week. Our main objective was to share and discuss new technologies in cybersecurity.
- During this time, I mainly focused on researching and studying how Guardicore company's technology works in terms of data filtration. I then presented my findings to my colleagues.
- Participated in big online workshop meetings with foreign companies from Singapore and India. Through these meetings, I had the opportunity to learn more about their technologies, including Kong, Opswat, and Block Armour, and how they defend against cyber viruses.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

#2 PROJECT NAME: QUT OLD GOVERNMENT HOUSE AR SIMULATOR

Role: Game (or Simulator) Developer and Level Creator

Wicked Storytelling, Brisbane, QLD | 02/2022 - 11/2022

Task: Created a simulator of an AR app used in the QUT Old Government House

- Worked in a group of four (three in the next stage as one member withdrew from the project) and implemented the simulator's features with another programming team member. Specifically, I fixed the user's virtual camera and created interactive radios, doors, and menus using C#. I was also responsible for creating the main menu.
- To create the level, I generated a Unity Scene based on the Old Government House and used ProBuild to do so. Additionally, I researched the historical objects that used to be in the Old Government House and their positions.
- Modelled 3D objects with Blender: chairs, tables, stairs, cabinets, and doors.
- Using Blender, I modeled 3D objects such as chairs, tables, stairs, cabinets, and doors. I also created condensed game design documents to clearly define the product's features, performance, interface, and user experience.
- Throughout the project, I collaborated with the development, design, and testing teams to ensure the product was completed to the highest quality.

#1 PROJECT NAME: CODING IN THE PARK

Role: Web Front-end Developer

QUT, Brisbane, QLD | 02/2019 - 11/2019

Task: Developed of STEM education website

- Worked in a group of five and was responsible for designing and implementing the website's front-end using HTML and CSS. I also contributed to the development of back-end interaction using MySQL and PHP. Additionally, I created a few games on the website using JavaScript, specifically puzzle games.
- To ensure that the product was clearly defined, I created product requirement documents outlining the product's features, performance, interface, and user experience.

• Throughout the project, I collaborated closely with the development, design, and testing teams to ensure the product was completed to the highest quality. I provided regular updates to the Scrum Master to maintain team efficiency.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF GAMES AND INTERACTION ENVIRONMENTS (Game Design)

Queensland University of Technology

02/2020 - 11/2022

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (Information Systems)

Queensland University of Technology

02/2017 - 11/2019

SKILLS

- Tools: Visual Studio, Git, Unity Engine, Unreal Engine, Blender, Xamarin, Android Studio, Microsoft
- Game Design, Programming, Theory and Mechanics, Web and App development
- Data/ Business Analysis
- Database Management, Data Structures and Algorithm Modelling, Information Security
- Programming languages: C#, C++, (HTML), CSS, Java and JavaScript, MySQL